Do you think Jeffrey Epstein was a spy?
>> I believe very strongly he was a spy.
Yes.
>> And who do you think he was working for?
>> The Israelis. I'm confident it was the
Israelis.
>> Why?
>> CIA whistleblower John Kiryaku is
absolutely certain that Jeffrey Epstein
was working for Israel as a spy. And if
you watch this channel regularly, you
know there's documented proof of that
from the email leaks. But I thought it
was interesting how he approached this
question as a former CIA operative, a
heroic one in fact, one of the few that
blew the cover off CIA torture program.
So, let's see what John has to say.
Please like the video and subscribe to
the channel. Jeffrey Epstein
is kind of the stereotypical example
that they give you in training for
what's called an access agent. This is a
different kind of recruit. So, for
example, if you're a foreign
intelligence service and you want
information like close-in information
from a former president,
from the CEO of the biggest company in
the world, from a member of the British
royal family, you're not going to
recruit these guys. You're not going to
recruit Bill Clinton or Bill Gates or
Prince Andrew. So, you do the next best
thing. You recruit somebody who has
regular access to them. And that person
that you recruit is going to need to
make these people feel comfortable and
appreciated.
And so you give them plenty of money. So
he has this house on an island or he has
the whole island. And maybe you bring in
young girls, you get them in
compromising positions just in case you
need to use what's called compromat
compromising
pictures. We know we know now that
Jeffrey Epstein's house on the island
had video cameras,
hidden video cameras in literally every
room, including the bathrooms. Yeah.
You'll notice when they interviewed
Galileain Maxwell just last year, she
lied about this, saying, "Hey, I knew
about the plans. I knew about the homes
and they didn't have cameras all over."
But the documented evidence, including
pictures taken from the FBI, show that
there were cameras. And indeed, I think
Epstein was an access agent, not a badge
carrying member of Mossad or the CIA.
But they did recruit him for this
service, this service of blackmail that
they denied for so long, despite the
fact that again, the Epstein file
releases, even though we don't have
everything. Of course, they never give
us everything. Some of the ones we do do
show that there were co-conspirators.
The FBI was investigating it and sex
trafficking was one of the angles they
were investigating.
Why?
Why would he care what was going on
unless it was to use that information
against people? As I said, only the
Israelis and the Russians use
extortion as a motivator.
So would they have made Jeffrey Epstein
rich?
>> Yeah.
>> In order to give him that access.
>> How could they have done that?
>> Oh, that's easy. I mean, you you do I
mean, governments are the only ones
really that can money that can launder
money unfettered.
>> Think about that. Governments are the
only ones that can money launder
unfettered. And of course you see this
happening in terms of war profiteering
to the military-industrial complex as
well to Rathon and Loheed Martin and
Boeing and and uh general dynamics. You
see this in so many ways in the war
regime just as it is in CIA espionage.
And the only thing I have a question on
is I don't think that Mossad and the
Russians are the only ones that use
extortion as a mechanism. The whole US
government is built on extortion, too.
And promising people free stuff,
supposedly free. It's not free. There's
no such thing as a free lunch if you
vote their way. So, they do that as a
scop in the general populace far beyond
even espionage. And you can also do it
through real estate, through fine art,
and through horses. Those are the three
easiest ways to launder money today.
Fine art, real estate, and raceh horses.
But presumably
he would have spoken out at some point,
no? He would have said something or
>> No, but it would explain why he got a
sweetheart deal in 2006. I mean, this is
a guy that's been convicted of child sex
crimes
and he gets 6 months of house arrest
with an ankle bracelet. We have
mandatory minimums in this country.
That's a 5-year mandatory minimum of
first offense.
>> He definitely had some interesting
power, didn't he?
>> Yeah. There were over 40 witnesses in
that first case that resulted in a
sweetheart deal in 2008. And by the way,
before that was all finalized, he flew
to Israel prepared apparently to invoke
the home law, the law of return, which
would have allowed him to become an
Israeli citizen. And guess which country
doesn't send back sex criminals to the
United States? Yeah. Our greatest ally
in the Middle East, Israel does not
allow the extradition of sex criminals
back. So he was prepared to go there and
escape those charges. But like I said,
he did get a sweetheart deal. This was
absurd. Over 40 witnesses against him
with the head prosecutor, Alex Acasta,
the US attorney, I should say, saying
that I was told to lay off Epstein
because Epstein was intelligence. This
is part of the case record. He said that
to Trump's transition team as they were
coming to power because they
entertaining the notion of Alex Aosta
for labor secretary, a position he
eventually got where this was set.
>> Mhm. And
Alex Aosta, who was the prosecuting
attorney at the time and then later
became Secretary of Labor under Trump,
Trump won. Alex Aosta said that he was
ordered by the attorney general to give
Epstein the sweetheart deal. Well, who's
the only person that can order the
attorney general to do something? It's
the president
or maybe the attorney general. At the
time, I think it was uh Gonzalez.
Um so, Alberto Gonzalez. So, it's hard
to know, but there are only a few people
above Alex Acasta, that's for sure. And
you know, you can count him on less than
one hand. That's what's real. But we'll
probably never know the truth. And in
later interviews, he of course denied
saying this to try to run cover for
whoever told him this. Did not elaborate
beyond this. But at one point, we know
he said this. And it seems to have been
the truth. That seems to have been the
truth, not what he said after.
>> So
was it because
>> Epstein was was working on Clinton? Most
of the people down there were Democrats.
I mean, what what was the reason?
>> Maybe he was working for the US
government.
>> It's possible that he could have been
doubled against the Israelis or others.
Sure. Sure, that's possible.
>> If you had to bet
>> Mhm.
>> what would you say if you had to bet
everything you have
on either him being a spy or not a spy?
>> Yeah.
>> What would you bet on?
>> He was a spy. I feel very confident in
that assessment.
I debated Alan Dersowitz about this on
the Pierce Morgan show one time. It was
it was Scott Horton and me who said that
he was an Israeli spy and it was Alan
Dersowitz and General Danny Ayalon, the
former head of Mossad.
Ayalon was kind of into it in terms of
having a fun time. He was just having a
fun time with the conversation. He
wasn't going to admit to anything.
Durowitz was Epstein's attorney.
So I said that that I believed Epstein
was an Israeli spy. And Durowitz
interrupts me like attorneys do. And he
says, "That is outrageous. If he had
been a spy, he would have told me
because I was his attorney and I could
have gone to the White House and I could
have gotten him a better sentence." And
I said, "Wait a minute. You could have
gone to the White House to say, "Go easy
on Jeffrey Epstein because he's an
Israeli spy collecting information from
American politicians. If I were the
president, I would have hung him from a
tree."
And then Piers Morgan said, "General I
Allen, was he a spy?" And he goes,
"Who knows?"
That says it all. Right. I I have to
disagree, though. Israel has its talents
in the US president and the US
presidency in general before Trump
enough that I don't know that the US
president would have responded in a way
that us real Americans, real people
would have wanted when it comes to ties
between Epstein and Israel. He did get a
sweetheart deal the first time. I'm not
sure that would have convinced him the
second time, but props to our friend
Scott Horton who will appear on the show
sometime soon. It just seems like
there's too many roads pointing to
Epstein's associations as an access
agent on behalf of Israel, specifically
Mossad with all the connections he had,
specifically to Ehood Barack, the former
head of IDF intelligence, who was the
prime minister and the defense minister.
And we know from the email leaks Epstein
wrote at least one full speech for that
he delivered in I think 2014. We also
know that Epstein literally brokered
security arrangements between the
government of Israel and the government
of the Ivory Coast and also the
of Mongolia. Martaza Hussein and Ryan
Grim from Drop Site have brought forward
those stories. We know from the email
leaks that Epstein was arranging wire
transfers with a prominent spy known spy
in Israel named Yoni Corin. That can be
discerned from the email leaks. and he
was actually setting up back channels
with his buddy Ehoud Barack and Vladimir
Putin to try to profit off of the Syrian
civil war to bring in funds. He also
served as a recruiter to build the
Leviathan field. This is a field to the
west of Hifa in Israel that Netanyahu
announced, you know, the initiation of
in December of last year, just one month
ago announced this. Well, who kind of
recruited and marketed that project for
investors? At the start it was Jeffrey
Epstein. And again, we know this from
the email leaks. All these things line
up with Epstein literally working on
behalf of Israel probably as an access
agent and probably gaining blackmail on
the most prominent people in the world.
This is what he did. This was what his
function was. And that explains why
there's such a diligent effort to cover
this up. both by Trump, both by Biden,
both by Clinton refusing to appear for a
subpoena, of course. And they're never
going to get charged for it. They're
never even going to interview Les
Wexner, who gave him enormous amounts of
inexplicable wealth that you just can't
explain organically, including a $77
million home, the biggest home in
Manhattan. The FBI has never questioned
that man, even though the email leaks
show he was possibly one of 10
co-conspirators with Epstein, and he was
set to be interviewed for subpoena so
that he could testify in front of a
grand jury. They still haven't
interviewed him. That email came from
2019, and they still haven't talked to
him. No answers, just pure corruption
from the highest levels of the deep
state. But thankfully, we have people
like Cash Patel and Dan Bonino to bring
us the truth, right? No, not at all.
They were involved in the cover up as
long as anyone else was. And that's what
you get out of this corrupt
administration. It's not just this one.
It's the previous one, too. It's not
like Biden ever promised any answers on
Epstein. And much of the liberal
establishment has only latched on to
Epstein when it became politically
convenient. In the Biden term, they used
Russia gate and they used, you know,
other weapons to attack Trump, not
Epstein. And most of them said this is
just a kooky right-wing conspiracy
theory. The few that didn't and did talk
about this like Ron Widen did demand
answers and divulging to the Senate the
wire transfers were known to have
happened between Epstein and people of
prominence that resulted in over a
billion dollars in transfers. I don't
think we'll ever get those either. But
that's where we are here. I don't think
we'll ever get the full unvarnished
truth. What we have gotten shows beyond
a shadow of a doubt, it's not a
conspiracy that Epstein worked on behalf
of Israel. There's so many different
connections now. We know and thanks to
the heroics of Drop Site News, we have
several of them laid out in a great
article series that I really recommend
to all you. So, that's what we have. I
side with John Kiryaku. He for sure was
an Israeli spy. He might have been
working as a free agent like Robert
Maxwell did for most of his life.
probably partnering with the CIA, maybe
MI6, who knows? But the connections to
Israel are by far the most ironclad. But
what do you guys think? Let me know in
the comments down below. Great segment.
I appreciate Diary of a CEO for this
interview. Really interesting interview
all the way through. And John always is.
I'm going to try to get him on the
channel as well. I would love to chat
with him about some of this stuff. So,
we'll see if we can do that. Also,
please like the video and subscribe to
the channel and consider joining as a
YouTube member. If you do that, you can
click the join button down below and
help support the channel. And in return
for that, I'll give you access to all my
videos before they go live to the
general public on YouTube. Also, if you
want a free copy of my first book,
Compact of the Republic, click the link
in the description below that will just
send you to a website. You plug in your
email, I'll send you a free copy of that
book free of charge, no obligation, just
because I appreciate you. And until I
see you guys next time, I have a few
demands, but I won't budge from them.
there. No more war, no more debt, no
more inflation, and no more empire.
Peace out, guys.